Southern New England Telephone Company Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series XI: Photographs undated, 1878-1998
  - Slides
    - Tray 7 (Box 532)
      - Support Services Annual Meeting (R. Ekstrom), 1982 March 20
      - Echlin Manufacturing Co., 1981 August
      - TEMCOM Dialing Instructions Pamphlet, [1980?]
      - Comptrollers (Tom Sheriden), 1982 June 17
      - SNET Logos (History)
      - Old Central Office Switch
    - Tray 8
      - Minority Business and Vendor Certification (R. Delany), 1979 July 18
      - Porta Typewriter Transmitter
      - ESS and Workers (by Joe Z.)
      - Service Reps
      - Signs
    - Tray 9
      - Buildings SNET Central Offices
      - Buildings SNET Central Offices
      - Buildings SNET 227 Church Street
      - Long Wharf March itime and Crossroads Building, 1990 April
      - Homes/Suburbs
    - Tray 10
      - Data Center
      - Lap-top Computer Transmitter
      - Emergency 911 Child Dialing Telephone
      - Video Conferencing
      - ATM in use
      - Flip-phone
      - Portaphone
      - Pager 2000
      - SLIK Cabinet
      - Fax
    - Tray 11
      - SONET Fiber Ring
      - Fiber Optics
      - Fiber Splicing
      - Memory Porta-printer for the Deaf, 1988 December
      - ESS Warning Lights
      - Miscellaneous Photos (by Joe Z.), 1991-1993
    - Tray 12
      - Locator
      - Students Links
      - Advertising Photos
        (includes historical)
      - Cell Site
      - Nurse w/computer and medical forms
      - Disasters - Storm, 1991 August
    - Tray 13 (Box 533)
      - Alfred Van Sinderen, President SNET
      - “Technology in the 80s”
      - Corporate Relations Personnel
    - Tray 14
      - Corporate Relations Personnel
      - New York SSA 50th Anniversary Meeting
      - Emergency 911
    - Tray 15
      - Corporate Relations Personnel
    - Tray 16
      - Special Olympics World Games, 1995
      - Plant Construction Fiber and Copper Comparison
      - SNET and Connecticut
      - SNET and Connecticut (historical)
    - Tray 17
      - SNET Personnel
      - Jean Handley, 1982, 1985
      - Daniel J. Miglio
      - Bob Neal
      - Walter Montieth
    - Tray 18
      - Warren Raynor
      - Jeanne Kardos
      - SNET Personnel [Corp Relations/Creative Services?]
  - Negatives
    - 35 Millimeter Film (filed by SNET job #) (gaps)
      - 1836-5974, 1953-1964 (Box 534)
      - 6000-7993, 1964-1968 (Box 535)
      - 8020-8865, 1968-1970 (Box 536)
      - 8866-9499, 1970-1971 (Box 537)
      - 9500-10198, 1971-1973 (Box 538)
      - 10200-10998, 1973-1975 (Box 539)
      - 11006-12799, 1975-1983 (Box 540)
      - 12801-13595, 1983-1994 (Box 541)
      - Miscellaneous Topics (unprocessed), 1979-1982 (Box 542)
      - Miscellaneous Topics (unprocessed), 1980-1982 (Box 543)